Ganesh Narawade WEB DEVELOPER

PHONE: 021 02458501

EMAIL: ganesh9211@hotmail.com

PORTFOLIO https://ganesh9211-dev.github.io/portfolio/

Visa Status: NZ Permanent Resident

GITHUB: https://github.com/ganesh9211-dev

Summary

I am a highly motivated, self taught Web Developer with a passion for software development and learning. I embrace challenges, offer diverse experiences, and am an agile learner. I have just completed Industry Connect boot camp which gave me 300 hours of a simulated work environment, where I worked on several apps and learned a lot. I am excited to bring my passion for IT and my positive attitude of making clients happy from my hospitality background to the tech world.

Skill Highlights

TECHNICAL:

- Web Development
- User Interface design
- Application Support
- JavaScript (ES6), React.js
- Material UI
- HTML5, CSS3
- Bootstrap
- Node.js, NPM
- RESTful APIs
- SQL databases
- Git, GitHub

PERSONAL:

- Team player In my previous career, I have been part of diverse teams where team work was paramount.
- Problem Solving I love problem solving and code error finding, I always check logically about errors and deep dive into it to sort it out.
- Fast learner Learned how to build complex designs for my personal projects in a short amount of time.
- Works well under pressure A skill I perfected during my time in the fast-paced environment in the hospitality industry e.g. handled 4 big functions at one time.
- Professional Communication In my previous work environment,good communication was the key asset to have as I had to communicate with different internal departments and fulfil clients requirement professionally for all events success e.g. dealing with International French rugby team management.

Experience

Portfolio

https://ganesh9211-dev.github.io/portfolio

Full Stack .Net Developer (Intern) MVP Studios, Wellington

March 2019 - August 2019

Talent-Onboarding Project

Worked as a full-stack developer for the Talent project, front end was on ReactJS and Webpack, hosted on Azure.

- Learned full-stack web development technologies, including front-end frameworks and SQL databases.
- Attended and contributed to the daily scrums and strategizing the workflow according to the project.
- Introduced state management to the team.
- Writing services for API's (C#, Net)
- Designing the UI's for the web using React and SemanticUI (bootstrap library for react)
- Gained experience with web technologies such as C# web services architecture, front end technologies (React, Webpack), introduced state management to the team to re-designed the parts of front end and modified services, learned and implemented Agile and SCRUM methodologies.

Conference & Events Supervisor

March 2015 - March 2020

The Rydges Hotel, Wellington

- Efficiency in planning and organising various events and ensure customer satisfaction.
- Assist and direct the team to ensure a high level of service is executed. Strong attention to detail.
- Make rosters, order beverages & linen, also plan for future events.
- Work with the Accounting department to track the payment to all vendors & service providers.
- Own the planning and delivery for all front of house aspects of the event.
- Actively ensure customer satisfaction through direct interaction with customers
- Generate revenue & wage cost report & send it to Food and Beverage Manager on daily basis.
- Proficient working knowledge of computers, Microsoft Excel, Word and Outlook.
- Resolving inter-departmental & staff conflicts.

Food & Beverage Supervisor (Restaurant & Conference)	
Abel Tasman Hotel, Wellington	

September 2013 – March 2015

Food & Beverage Supervisor (Restaurant & Conference)

The Rydges Hotel, Wellington

December 2010 – September 2013

Food & Beverage Attendant (Fine Dine Restaurant)

White House Restaurant, Wellington

October 2010 - March 2011

Food & Beverage Attendant (5 star luxury hotel)

The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, India

January 2010 – June 2010

Food & Beverage Attendant (4 star deluxe hotel)

Parabola Restaurant, Rodas Mumbai, India

April 2009 - December 2009

Food & Beverage Attendant (4 star hotel)

The Rembrandt Hotel London, UK

October 2006 – October 2008

Education

React.js Course	CODE ACADEMY	2020 – 2020
JavaScript for beginners' basics Course	Mosh Courses	2020 – 2020
Software Development Boot Camp course	INDUTRY CONNECT	2018 - 2019
Bachelor of Hospitality Management degree (level -7)	Wellington Institute of Technology (WelTec	e) 2010 - 2011
Hospitality Management -Postgraduate Diploma	London school of Business and Computing	2007 - 2008
Hospitality Management -Advanced Diploma	London school of Business and Computing	2006 - 2007
Twin Diploma in Hospitality Management	Rizvi college of Hotel Management	2003 - 2005

References

Lakhan DeshPande from LPS New Zealand

Sarabh Sathe from SKYCITY Entertainment Group

Email: saurya271@gmail.com

Email: <u>deshpandelakhan@gmail.com</u>

Mobile no- 022 303 4554 Mobile no- 0210 313 586

WIODIIE 110- U22 3U3 4554